https://www.ciare.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Ciare is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Ciare Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Ciare website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Ciare collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Ciare also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Ciare. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Ciare for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Ciare Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Ciare public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Ciare does not read any of your private online communications.
Ciare encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Ciare so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Ciare is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Ciare and Ciare family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Ciare collects and uses your personal information to operate the Ciare Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Ciare also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Ciare and its affiliates. Ciare may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Ciare does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Ciare may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Ciare may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Ciare, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Ciare does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Ciare keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Ciare, in order to determine what Ciare services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Ciare to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Ciare Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Ciare or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Ciare; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Ciare, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Ciare Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Ciare pages, or register with Ciare site or services, a cookie helps Ciare to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Ciare Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Ciare features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Ciare services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Ciare secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Ciare secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Ciare will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Ciare encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Ciare is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Ciare welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Ciare has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Ciare at fabio.parigi@grupposinapsi.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Utilizziamo i cookie per essere sicuri che tu possa avere la migliore esperienza sul nostro sito. Se continui ad utilizzare questo sito noi assumiamo che tu ne sia felice.OkPrivacy policy
